marvelvscapcom3.com 2017-06-14

# Capcom Privacy Policy

**

**

## CAPCOM USA ONLINE PRIVACY STATEMENT

Last updated May 11, 2016

Here is a PDF version of our Privacy Policy for those who wish to save or print the contents of this page.

Welcome to Capcom USA!

**OUR PRIVACY COMMITMENT**

Capcom U.S.A., Inc. (collectively, "Capcom USA", "Capcom", or "we") respect the privacy rights of our online visitors and recognizes the importance of protecting all information that you may choose to share with us. To further this commitment, we have adopted this Online Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to guide how we collect, store, and use the information you provide us.

This Privacy Policy and the ESRB certification seals shown on our websites confirm that Capcom USA is a member in good standing of the Entertainment Software Rating Board's Privacy Certified Program ("ESRB"). To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative and all of our websites where this Privacy Policy is posted have been reviewed and certified by ESRB Privacy Certified to meet established online information collection, use, and disclosure practices. As a licensee of this privacy program, we are subject to frequent audits of our websites and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by the ESRB.

**TABLE OF CONTENTS**

**Q1.**What information does this Privacy Policy cover?  
**Q2.**What types of information do we collect about you?  
**Q3.**How is your information used and shared?  
**Q4.**What are your California Privacy Rights?  
**Q5.**What kinds of security measures do we take to safeguard your personally identifiable information?  
**Q6.**How can you update your personal information and profile?  
**Q7.**How can you ask questions, or send us comments, about this Privacy Policy?  
**Q8.**How will you know if we amend this Privacy Policy?  
**Q9.**How is information treated when it is collected from non-US residents?

## • Q1. What information does this Privacy Policy cover?

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected on the websites where this Privacy Policy is posted, and does not apply to any other information collected by Capcom USA through any other means. This Privacy Policy applies to use and sharing of information collected on and after the date that this Privacy Policy is posted.

Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information submitted and collected online, and does not apply to information that may be collected by Capcom USA offline. This Privacy Policy applies only to websites maintained by Capcom USA, and not to Capcom Game Studio Vancouver, Inc. (www.capcomvancouver.com), our international affiliates (Capcom Asia, Capcom Europe, Capcom Japan), our mobile applications, or any websites or mobile applications maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link. Capcom USA is therefore not responsible for the content or activities provided on those websites.

Once you have clicked on an advertisement or a third party link and have left our websites, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you must read the privacy policy of the advertiser/third party to see how your information will be handled on its website.

Finally, the terms of this Privacy Policy are subject to all applicable laws.

(Back to top)

## • Q2. What types of information do we collect about you?

With the exception of your Internet Protocol address ("IP address"), we do not require personal information to access our website. However, if you prefer not to disclose personal information, you will not be able to enjoy certain features of our website. Personal information is information that can be used to directly identify and contact you.

**These Websites and Children**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from users under the age of 13 ("Child" or "Children"). We take Children's privacy seriously and encourage parents to play an active role in their Children's online experience at all times.

If Capcom learns that a Child's personally identifiable information has been collected, we will delete the account. If parents believe that we have unintentionally collected their Child's personal information, they should contact us to request the deletion of the information.

**Capcom USA**  
Attn.: Privacy Policy Administrator  
185 Berry Street, Suite 1200  
San Francisco, CA 94107  
(650) 350-6500  

**Personal Information You Provide to Us**

All of the personal information we receive comes directly from our guests. To offer our guests certain features on our websites, we collect several types of personal information. We collect personal information from our guests to:

  * Register for an account on our website 
  * Register for our community forum 
  * Register for our newsletter 
  * Use "Tell-a-Friend" features 
  * Purchase a product at one of our online stores 
  * Participate in contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions 
  * Receive customer or technical support 
  * Participate in online surveys, polls, or questionnaires 
  * Register a product 

Typically, this information includes:

  * name 
  * e-mail address 
  * telephone and fax number 
  * shipping and billing address 
  * credit card information (for those purchasing products online) 

Please note that the purchase information collected through the Capcom store at http://shop.capcom.com/ is handled by Digital River, Inc. and is therefore governed by Digital River's privacy policy. We encourage you to review their privacy policy carefully, and may reach out to them directly with any questions you have regarding their privacy practices:

Digital River, Inc.  
ATTN: Privacy Department  
10380 Bren Road West  
Minnetonka, MN 55343

**Non-Personal Information You Provide to Us**

Additionally, we may also collect other types of non-personal information (known as demographic information) such as your age or date of birth, gender, hobbies, occupation, marital status, platform preferences, and other game ownership information. This demographic information may be combined with your personal information.

**Information Collected Through Social Networking Sites**

You can also engage with our websites on or through third-party social networking websites, such as Facebook and Twitter, or other third-party social media plug-ins and applications. When you engage with our websites on or through third-party social networking websites, plug-ins and applications, you may allow us to have access to certain information from your social media profile (e.g., name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, the posts or the "likes" you make) to deliver content or as part of the operation of the application. We may also obtain non-personally identifiable information (e.g., content viewed, game performance, high scores, and information about advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on) from your interaction with our websites.

When you provide information from your social media account, it can help enable us to do things like:

  * give you exclusive content 
  * personalize your online experience with us within and outside our applications or websites 
  * contact you through the social networking websites or directly by sending you the latest news, special offerings, and rewards 

By doing so, you consent to the use of this information in accordance with our Privacy Policy. When you provide personal information to us through an application, on our websites, or on social networking websites, it may be publicly viewed by other members of these websites and we cannot prevent further use of the information by third parties.

**Information Collected Through Technology**

We collect information through technology to make our websites more interesting and useful to you. For example, when you come to one of our websites, we collect your IP address. An IP address is often associated with the portal through which you enter the Internet, like your ISP (Internet Service Provider), your company, or your university. At times, we use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our websites.

**Cookies**

Our websites also use cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that a website sends to your computer while you are viewing the website. We and other companies use cookies for a variety of purposes. For example, when you return to one of our websites after logging in, cookies provide information to the website so that the website will remember who you are. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You can do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer or Firefox) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's help menu to learn the correct way to modify your settings. If you turn cookies off, you will not have access to many features that make your web experience smoother, like the features mentioned above, and some of our services may not function properly.

When visiting Capcom's websites, the third-party cookies that may be present include, but are not limited to those listed in the chart below.

**Cookies Used**

 Cookie name  |  Source  |  Expiry  | Purpose | How to block  
---|---|---|---|---  
_utma | Google Analytics | 2 years from set/update | These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve our site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. | You may visit https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB to block these cookies. Alternatively, you can change your browser settings to accept or refuse these cookies as mentioned below.  
_utmb | Google Analytics | 30 minutes from set/update |  |   
_utmc | Google Analytics | Upon the browser closing |  |   
_utmv | Google Analytics | 2 years from the visitor's last visit |  |   
_utmz | Google Analytics | 6 months from set/update |  |   
  
YouTube (Google) | Cookies are used to deliver content on this website using YouTube (Google). Data collected by Google may also be used for other purposes, including advertising. | You can find out more about Google's privacy practices and the cookies that it uses via YouTube here (http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). You can also change your browser settings to accept or refuse these cookies as mentioned below.   
---|---|---  
Twitter | Twitter uses cookies to enable visitors to share website pages and content through third party social networking and other websites. Twitter may also use visitors' information to serve targeted advertising on other websites. | Further information about how Twitter uses cookies, including how you can opt-out is available here (https://twitter.com/privacy). You can also change your browser settings to accept or refuse these cookies as mentioned below.   
Facebook | Cookies are used to deliver content on this website using Facebook. Data collected by Facebook may also be used for other purposes, including advertising. | You can find out more about Facebook's privacy practices and the cookies that it uses here (https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other). You can also change your browser settings to accept or refuse these cookies as mentioned below.   
MediaMind (__atuvs, __atuvc) | Streetfighter.com uses cookies to enhance their marketing campaign analytics gathering. Data collected is only available to marketing team involved with the product and is not shared. | Further information about how Mediamind uses cookies, including how you can opt-out is available here (http://www.mediamind.com/privacy-policy). You can also change your browser settings to accept or refuse these cookies as mentioned below.   
  
(Back to top)

## • Q3. How is your information used and shared?

Whatever the purpose may be, we will only collect information to the extent reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives.

**Capcom USA Activities and Updates**

Information collected from those who voluntarily submit it to us is used to provide services like newsletter subscriptions, updates on special events, game news, and e-mail announcements of interest to our users. 

**Forums, Blogs, and Message Boards**

If you register for access to our blogs or message boards, we will use your personal information to enable you to view and post messages on the boards. You should understand, however, that community forums, blogs, and message boards are tools that allow you to communicate with members of the online community. So whenever you give out personal information in public areas, that information can be collected and used by people you don't know.

Should you wish to remove content or information after you have posted it, you may do so by logging into your Capcom account and clicking either the "garbage can" or "x" icon located on your post. Alternatively, you may contact us at [privacy@capcom.com](mailto:privacy@capcom.com) with your request. In addition, Capcom provides all registered users the ability to completely and permanently delete their account information including all comments, blogs, and forum posts. To delete your Capcom-Unity account, please log in and visit this link: <http://www.capcom-unity.com/help/remove_user.one>. **Please note that deleting your profile _cannot_ be reversed.**

Please also note that removal of this content or information from public view does not guarantee complete or comprehensive removal. After your removal request has been honored, we may retain copies of the content or information you have previously posted on our servers. We are not required to remove your posted content or information if it has been rendered anonymous or if we are required by law to retain it. Additionally, we do not have control over third parties (e.g., other users) who may have copied or reposted this information.

**Operational Uses**

We may also use your personal information for other purposes such as "Operational Uses." For example, we may use your information to send you administrative communications either about your account with us or about features of our websites.

We occasionally employ other companies to perform services necessary to our internal operations. For example, we have partnered with other companies to personalize our web pages, process credit card transactions, analyze customers' interactions with our websites, and process consumer surveys. We also provide postal addresses to the U.S. Post Office for delivery purposes. While providing their services, these companies may access your personally identifying information. These companies have agreed to securely store and maintain the personal information received from us.

**Aggregate Information**

Finally, we may take your personally identifiable information and make it non-personally identifiable. We do this either by combining it with information about other individuals (aggregating your information with information about other individuals), or by removing characteristics (e.g., your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you. This process is known as de-personalizing your information. Given the non-personal nature of this information, no restrictions apply under this Privacy Policy on our right to de-personalize your personal information. We may use de-personalized information in any way and share it with third parties without your consent.

**Business Information**

For practical reasons, we treat personal information submitted to us in a business capacity different from information we receive in a non-business capacity. Personal information submitted to us in a business capacity (e.g., resumes) may be shared with third parties, depending on the nature of the inquiry.

**Purchase or Sale of Businesses**

From time to time, we may purchase a business or sell one or more of our businesses and your personally identifiable information may be transferred as a part of the purchase or sale. If we purchase a business, the personally identifiable information received with that business would be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy, if it is practicable and permissible to do so. If we sell a business, we will include provisions in the selling contract requiring the purchaser to treat your personally identifiable information in the same way required by this Privacy Policy (including any amendments to this Privacy Policy). The provisions of this paragraph will also apply if we are sold as part of bankruptcy proceedings.

**Third Party Use**

Our company does not share and has not reserved the right to rent or sell personal or demographic information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

**Disclosures Required By Law and Disclosures to Help Protect the Security and Safety of Our Websites and Others**

We will disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that disclosure is required by law (e.g., court order or subpoena) or to help:

  * enforce our Terms of Service, or contest, sweepstakes, promotions, or game rules; 
  * protect your safety or security, including the safety and security of your property; or 
  * protect the safety and security of our websites or third parties. 

(Back to top)

## • Q4. What are your California Privacy Rights?

Since 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. However, as previously stated, we do not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you still have inquiries regarding our disclosure policy, please contact us:

Capcom USA  
Attn.: Privacy Policy Administrator  
185 Berry Street, Suite 1200  
San Francisco, CA 94107  
(650) 350-6500  

(Back to top)

## • Q5. What kinds of security measures do we take to safeguard your personally identifiable information?

The security and confidentiality of your information is extremely important to us. We have technical, administrative and physical security measures in place to protect your personal information from unauthorized access and improper use. We also review our security procedures periodically to consider appropriate new technology and updated methods. But, despite our best efforts, no security measure is ever perfect or impenetrable. Specific security measures we currently implement to prevent unauthorized physical or electronic access to web users' personal and demographic information:

  * Web user data is stored behind a firewall 
  * Data is stored in a secure physical environment (e.g. behind locked doors) 
  * Data is stored in a database accessible to authorized employees on a need-to-know basis only 
  * Users or employees must have a unique password before gaining access to user data 
  * We use standard encryption technology when transferring or receiving sensitive personal information like credit card numbers 
  * We maintain written security policies to which all employees must adhere. 

(Back to top)

## • Q6. How can you update your personal information and profile?

You can access and update the contact information you gave us during registration (that is, your e-mail address or any other information that would directly enable us to contact you), by e-mailing us at [accounts@capcom.com](mailto:accounts@capcom.com). You may update the information in your profile by logging into your account and visiting your account settings.

(Back to top)

## • Q7. How can you ask questions, or send us comments, about this Privacy Policy?

If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us with questions or comments at:

Capcom USA  
Attn.: Privacy Policy Administrator  
185 Berry Street, Suite 1200  
San Francisco, CA 94107  
(650) 350-6500  

Any personal information you provide to the above e-mail and postal mail addresses will not be used to send you promotional materials, unless you request it.

Capcom is a licensee of the ESRB's Privacy Certified Program. If you believe that we have not properly responded to your inquiry, please contact the ESRB at <http://www.esrb.org/privacy/contact.jsp>, or:

ESRB  
Attn.: Privacy Certified Program  
420 Lexington Avenue, Suite 2024  
New York, NY 10170  

(Back to top)

## • Q8. How will you know if we amend this Privacy Policy?

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material changes in how we collect, use, or share your personal information, we will send you a private message on Capcom-Unity.com and prominently post a notice of the changes on the websites covered by this Privacy Policy. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective when posted, and your continued use of any of the websites covered by the Privacy Policy after the posting will constitute your acceptance of and agreement to be bound by those changes.

(Back to top)

## • Q9. How is information treated when it is collected from non-US residents?

Personal information collected on our websites may be stored and processed in the United States. By using our websites you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Capcom complies with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Capcom has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Capcom’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

(Back to top)
